<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Bufu Blog</title><link>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Bufu Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:40:51 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bufu-sec.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSL with pfSense and the Draytek Vigor167</title><link>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/pfsense_draytek_telekom_dsl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:40:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/pfsense_draytek_telekom_dsl/</guid><description>Using DSL with pfSense and the Draytek Vigor167 Switching from a FritzBox modem router to a Draytek dedicated modem in bridge mode can be a game changer for anyone looking to take control of their home or small office network. The FritzBox, while a popular choice, can be restrictive and annoying to use, with many features locked or hidden away in menus. By using a dedicated modem in bridge mode, you can bypass these limitations and enjoy the full range of features that your router has to offer.</description></item><item><title>TrueNAS Backup to Backblaze</title><link>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/truenas_backup_to_backblaze/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:37:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/truenas_backup_to_backblaze/</guid><description>Backing up TrueNAS datasets with Backblaze Are you tired of being limited by storage restrictions when backing up your TrueNAS datasets? One solution is to use Backblaze, a popular cloud storage provider. However, by using a personal version of Backblaze in combination with virtual drives, you can bypass these limitations and create unlimited backups of your important data. In this blog post, we will walk you through the process of setting up this backup solution, including creating a backup user in TrueNAS, setting permissions on the dataset, creating an SMB share, and mounting the share with Dokany.</description></item><item><title>Personal Knowledge Base</title><link>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/personal_knowledge_base/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 21:55:10 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://bufu-sec.com/posts/personal_knowledge_base/</guid><description>Introduction This article will teach you how to create your personal knowledge base, using the Hugo doks theme and hosting it on Github Pages. We will also be using a custom domain name, bought from namecheap.
Why Hugo and not a dedicated Note Taking App? So why use Hugo? This seems like a lot of work compared to using an already premade solution, such as Obsidian.</description></item></channel></rss>